Why are we forced to work?!
Why must we pay money
in order to eat?!
Can't we all just share?
The rich get fat
while the poor die!
Where is the true freedom
in this world?!
We are all slaves to our work!
And is work fun?
No! How could it be?!
We do not want to work, period!
That's why I, Hammerhead,
will change our society
into one where only those
who want to work will work,
while the rest are supported!
We will create a utopia!
The Paradisers led by me, Hammerhead,
will make all this a reality!
Boss, no one's listening.
What did you say?!
Bah! These civilians are idiots!
Let's go!
Zeniru's the richest man in town.
We'll wreck his posh penthouse
and show them we're serious!
High-rise apartments
are symbols of inequality!
- Yes, sir!
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
This whole building is Zeniru's home.
There's no way he made
so much money legally.
Unforgivable! Bring it down!
Yes, sir!
Target has been destroyed!
As expect from these powerful
experimental battle suits.{Hm, these experimental battle suits
sure pack a wallop.}
It was definitely worth risking
our lives to steal them.
Wait, that was the wrong building.
My bad, Boss.
Zeniru's house is a little further up.
Everyone makes mistakes!
The important thing is to learn
from them. Am I right?
Yes, you're right!
All right, let's go to Zeniru's apartment.
Thanks, bicycle guy!
Don't come asking to play rock, paper, scissor
with a booger on your finger!
A dream?
The terrorist group responsible
for the riots
call themselves the Paradisers.
They have destroyed
a high-rise building in City F.
The situation seems to
be spiraling out of control.
We have just learned
the identity of their leader.
m 0 0 l 500 0 500 110 0 110
B-CLASS CRIMINAL :
HAMMERHEAD
Hammerhead is a B-class criminal
who has been involved in several
violent incidents in the past.
He is a man of large stature,
standing 2.15m tall
and weighing 210kg.
According to one report,
he once fought 20 men
in a street brawl
and sent them all to the hospital.
The Paradisers sent the following
message to this TV station.
"We will continue to riot until food,
clothing and shelter
"are provided free of charge
to those who do not work,"
- amongst other unintelligible demands.
- Sounds pretty boring.
- Like Hammerhead, the group is
made up of unemployed young men
- with no motivation to work.
- No need for me to get involved.
- Also, the group members
all have shaven heads,
making them quite intimidating.
Those who encounter
any shaven-headed men on the street
are advised to leave
the area immediately.
What the hell?
But that's—
They stole
my look!
I spend all this time
trying to be a hero,
If they keep this up...{but if they keep acting
like this, I'll be treated}
Won't people start treating me
like a villain?!
I'm gonna smash them!
Run!
It's them!
The Paradisers are coming.
They aren't...
backing down!
This is too dangerous!
Stop right there, you pack of thugs!
The bicyclist for justice,
Mumen Rider, is here!
Mumen Rider has come to save us!
There's nothing to fear if he's here!
A hero? What a joke!
Here I go!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Mr. Zeniru, you must flee!
H-Hm. But running away
from terrorists
would hurt my reputation.
There's no need to leave.
You're a lucky man,
having this occur
while I'm still under contract.
But you're a bodyguard—
Oh, Sonic!
Can I leave this to you?
The men coming are—
Of course.
It's their lives you should worry about.
But please do think of a way to
dispose of the pile of dead bodies.
The Paradisers...
A bunch of upstarts equipped with
some new type of battle suit.
And B-class criminal Hammerhead.
He might have some backbone.
THE
MODERN NINJA
Boss, you can see Zeniru's building
across the woods.
People call it the Golden Turd.
All right, let's go!
Someone's here.
I've been waiting
for you, Hammerhead.
Zeniru sent me.
Let me start out by saying
No opponent of mine has
ever escaped alive.
I plan on keeping it that way.
When it comes to my job,
I'm a perfectionist.
But if you surrender right now,
I'll let you live.
So, what will it be?
What is this?
What's going on?
Why is every—
Crap!
Bastard!
What are you trying to do?
Trying to intimidate me?
You can't see me, can you?
There you are!
It's a terrorist!
No, I'm not!
So he decided to fight
instead of running.
Oops, there goes
my bad habit again.
You're just a little dog bought
by Zeniru's money.
You think someone like me,
who fights for a noble cause,
can lose to a dog?!
Yes, I see what he's up to.
Just as I thought—
he's a complete fool.
Couldn't he have at least
tried to arrange the rocks
in a less obvious way?
There are plenty more rocks
where those came from!
If you don't stop me,
they'll keep coming.
So you think you'll be able
to deal with my speed
if you know which direction
I'm coming from?
How pathetic.
But I'll play along.
In fact,
I'll take you...
head on!
He's too fast. I can't see him.
But it doesn't matter if I can't.
Because of this!
Gotcha!
Think about how stupid
you were to face off against me
on your way down to Hell!
It's over.
Unfortunately,
I couldn't go easy on them.
Yes, Hammerhead's body is here too.
I'll head back now—
The body disappeared?
That was close!
Thank goodness he hit my head.
My skull always was several times
thicker than normal.
Dammit. I don't know
who that bastard was,
but one day I'm gonna kill—
Huh?
Now who's there?
Hm?
Oh, found you.
As with the mosquito monster,
I once again underestimated
my opponent's power.
I let my guard down and Kabuto
took advantage of that.
If Master Saitama had not been there,
I would certainly have been destroyed.
I see.
Well, I'm glad you're okay—
Doctor...
Master Saitama
saved my life twice.
You, Doctor Kuseno,
restored my life to me.
Later this same life was saved
by Master Saitama,
who now has saved it again.
Yes, I get the picture, Genos.
What you're trying to tell me is
how amazing
this Saitama fellow is, right?
Yes.
Genos, they're not ready just yet,
but I am developing
a new series of augmentations.
When I replace your existing parts
with these new ones,
you may be able to
surpass this Saitama.
I imagine he must possess
an enormous amount of strength
for you go on about him so.
Yes.
What's your deal?
You here to sign up
with the Paradisers?
No, that's wrong.
I'm just a guy who's a hero for fun.
For personal reasons,
I'm here to smash your heads in.
So, where are your followers?
Then, die!!
I need to get out of here quickly.
Huh?!
I thought I punched him?
What a letdown.
I was all excited
about these battle suits.
But the design is lame,
and all they do is give you
superhuman strength.
You have no idea how hard it was
to get hold of these things!
Bastard, how could you know their value?!
I've been looking for someone to
test the full power of this suit on!
Spin attack!
I used to use that move
all the time when I was a kid...
Huh?
No way...
Hammerhead, huh?
He's a lot like me.
What the hell are you?!
W-Wait. I just wanted
to get out of working...
Don't be bad anymore, okay?
Huh? So you're
not going to kill me?
- Get outta here.
- Okay!
Guess I'll go home.
Where did Hammerhead go?
There's no one left but you.
Hammerhead went that way.
Buck naked.
What's this?
Hey, you got it wrong.
What did I get wrong?
I'm not their comrade.
You're lying.
No, no, no.
Don't be dumb—look at me!
I don't need to.
With that bald head,
there's no denying it.
No.
Look! It's me. Me!
You know, the guy who's a hero for fun—
Never heard of you.
Oh, I see...
Either way, it doesn't matter.
You read my attacks. Twice.
That's the real problem.
Born in a ninja village,
I've been perfecting
my techniques since childhood.
Yet you saw right through them.
This I cannot allow.
What's he talking about?
My pride won't have it.
I don't care who you are,
I can't let you simply walk away.
Oh, come on.
You just want to try out
your moves on me.
I can tell by that innocent smile
of yours.
What do you think of this speed
that beats sound?
Of these shock waves?
Can you even see me?
How can you possibly
keep up with me?
Can I go home?
Bastard!
Wind Blade Kick!
Checkmate.
Ah, sorry!
That wasn't on purpose.
I meant to stop
before hitting you,
but your momentum carried
my fist into your...
WE ARE EXPERIENCING TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES.
PLEASE STAND BY
I've worked every job from
assassin to bodyguard.
I'm the best ninja.
I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
But I'm putting my work on hold.
Now that I've found such
a formidable opponent,
I'm dedicating myself to training
until we settle this.
Let me know your name.
It's Saitama.
Saitama!
Next time we meet,
it'll be your demise!
Okay.
I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic,
the ultimate ninja,
will bring you down without fail!
Train hard!
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic?
Who is that?
And who would possess such
a redundant name?
Dunno.
He suddenly appeared,
declared we were rivals,
and took off.
If he is a nuisance,
I will get rid of him.
Well, you're hardly different.
Actually, why are you here again?
Go home.
It's not like we're related.
Master, I must become stronger—
Shut up!
I'm now aware of a serious problem
and am reeling from shock.
So I beg you, go home for today.
A serious problem?
What could cause a problem
for someone as great as you?
Please tell me.
No one knows who I am.
It's been three years since
I first became a hero.
I've defeated many monsters and
evil organizations during that time.
I've never heard of any other heroes
doing as much as me.
Everyone in the world should
know me by now!
Isn't it weird that I don't have
any fans or anything?!
You know what he said to me today?
"Never heard of you."
Plus, everyone in town took me
for a terrorist.
They've all forgotten how
I beat those monsters for them!
He is right.
The news report did not mention
m 0 0 l 860 0 860 80 0 80
Mumen Rider Saves The Day
Master Saitama or Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
Instead, the credit for defeating the Paradisers
went to a hero called Mumen Rider.
Wait...
Master!
Are you listed with the Hero Registry?
HERO ASSOCIATION, OFFICIAL HOMEPAGE
"Take a test at any local branch
of the Hero Association.
"If you score better than the cut-off,
you will be registered in
the Hero Registry and
will be allowed to officially
call yourself a 'hero'."
"Once you are recognized
by the Association,
you are deemed a pro and
will get paid
from donations collected
by the Association."
"All heroes
in the public eye
are registered, professional heroes."
"You may be doing
plenty of hero work,
but self-proclaimed heroes
are really just weir...does..."
"...weirdoes spouting nonsense
viewed with suspicion."
I had no idea.
Genos, are you registered?
No. I feel no need to.
Let's register! Register with me
and I'll make you my disciple.
Let's go.
P-Please... F-Forgive me...
Pleading for his life after stealing
battle suits from the organization?
He truly understood nothing.
Of course,
we did let the theft take place
in order to collect data from
the suits in the field.
And the body?
Leave it.
Thanks for giving me
my thick skull...
Mommy.
I promise I'll get a job!
APPLICATION FOR HERO TEST
Our guest today is Mr. Majimeda,
an expert on the labor issues
confronting young people today.
Thank you for having me.
As we saw with
the Paradiser incident recently,
there's an increase in young people
who lack all motivation to work.
can you comment on this phenomenon?
-I'm not so different...
-Even in the case of the Paradisers,
I think they've been influenced
by irresponsible lyrics
in popular songs like
"Don't Give Up on Your Dreams"
and "Make Your Dreams Come True."
- ...from those unemployed guys.
- People who believe such hogwash
end up making excuses for themselves
and become discouraged.
One wrong step
and I could've been one of them.
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
So, shall we go, master?
Y-Yeah.
m 0 0 l 222 0 222 36 0 36
HERO TEST LOCATION #6
NEXT
EPISODE
THE ULTIMATE MENTOR
Err... I'm the recently reformed Hammerhead.
Before I introduce next week's episode,
I'd like to do a little PR for myself.
Oh? You won't allow that?
Next time on One Punch Man:
Episode 5, "The Ultimate Mentor."
Yeah, if I'd had a mentor like him,
maybe my life would've been different.